[{"answer": "I've been thinking, my friend, about my friend. I was going to ask if she'd come with me sometime to meet Dr. Woolens", "docId": "Ice-Storm_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I did, but", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "We don't have to always go to your club, dad", "docId": "Ice-Storm_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "-- Well what am I supposed to call you", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Just be careful", "docId": "Ice-Storm_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Tonight? my friend, he's been out of it since he was born", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Hello you two. Am I barging in on some kind of religious study group? my friend, you look marvelous. Will I see you and my friend at the my friend's", "docId": "Ice-Storm_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "And Reverend my friend? Did you make the list", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Thanks again. For the dinner", "docId": "Ice-Storm_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I used to know how to cook", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Because you like it on your turkey sandwiches", "docId": "Ice-Storm_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I... I think I am..", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I do. I'm", "docId": "Ice-Storm_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " You know my friend, I've been thinkin", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "You crying", "docId": "Ice-Storm_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " Whatever that means my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " Whatever that means my friend", "docId": "Ice-Storm_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You have to bring this up now? What? Did I do something here? Is that it? Is it something I did", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "You have to bring this up now? What? Did I do something here? Is that it? Is it something I did", "docId": "Ice-Storm_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " Hell, I know. I", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "With who", "docId": "Ice-Storm_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Libbets? What kind of a name is Libbets", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Maybe we can mess around. You know, only if you want to..", "docId": "Ice-Storm_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Why did you", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I don't know", "docId": "Ice-Storm_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Oh right. The mustache coffee cup. The one that was sitting on the dash", "docId": "Ice-Storm_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "That one", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "It wouldn't make a pleasant evening, if that's what you're after. I don't want to talk about it. Stupid mustache cup", "docId": "Ice-Storm_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Don't be dim", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Listen, my friend. I have obligations that precede your... from before you showed up. One or two, you know, goo", "docId": "Ice-Storm_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "How you take it isn't all that interesting to me, my friend. I'm sorry", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "My what", "docId": "Ice-Storm_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "And I have a special feeling too, because I do. It's special", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Hood residence", "docId": "Ice-Storm_-The.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Is this my friend", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": " my friend, what time is it", "docId": "Ice-Storm_-The.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "What time is it", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Is this my friend", "docId": "Ice-Storm_-The.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Um, te", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "You'll get some sleep on the couch out there", "docId": "Ice-Storm_-The.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "We'll talk in the morning", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "That's nice. Are you drunk", "docId": "Ice-Storm_-The.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I don't know either. You spin around, when you lie down", "qsentId": 44}]